{
  "level": 5,
  "unit": 1,
  "spelling": [
    {
      "week": "1",
      "words": [
        { "prompt": "The desks __________ out unevenly.", "answer": "jut" },
        { "prompt": "The __________ on her leg hurt.", "answer": "nick" },
        { "prompt": "The __________ word was the hardest.", "answer": "tenth" },
        { "prompt": "I __________ when I don't know.", "answer": "shrug" },
        { "prompt": "__________ the papers into your bag.", "answer": "stuff" },
        {
          "prompt": "It makes no __________ to wear a hat.",
          "answer": "sense"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The __________ air made my hair frizzy.",
          "answer": "damp"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "He slept in the __________ for a few hours.",
          "answer": "cot"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Don't __________ items across the room.",
          "answer": "fling"
        },
        { "prompt": "The __________ is at the edge.", "answer": "notch" },
        { "prompt": "I saw water __________ from the pipe.", "answer": "gush" },
        { "prompt": "__________ your homework for errors.", "answer": "scan" },
        { "prompt": "She graded a __________ of papers.", "answer": "batch" },
        { "prompt": "It was a __________ day at school.", "answer": "rough" },
        {
          "prompt": "He was sitting on a tree __________ .",
          "answer": "stump"
        },
        { "prompt": "That was a __________ word to spell.", "answer": "tough" },
        {
          "prompt": "My brother loves to __________ loudly.",
          "answer": "laugh"
        },
        { "prompt": "He took a __________ at the answer.", "answer": "guess" },
        { "prompt": "I __________ lead pencils to pens.", "answer": "prefer" },
        { "prompt": "A __________ is a symbol of peace.", "answer": "dove" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "2",
      "words": [
        { "prompt": "I need glue to __________ it down.", "answer": "paste" },
        { "prompt": "Sonya became Jake's __________ .", "answer": "bride" },
        { "prompt": "He used an ax to __________ !", "answer": "shave" },
        {
          "prompt": "It was full of flavor and __________ .",
          "answer": "spice"
        },
        { "prompt": "He had no __________ for money.", "answer": "greed" },
        { "prompt": "We had to __________ for help.", "answer": "plead" },
        { "prompt": "She ran to __________ me with a hug.", "answer": "greet" },
        { "prompt": "I raked leaves into a __________ .", "answer": "heap" },
        { "prompt": "A stranger __________ the bill.", "answer": "paid" },
        { "prompt": "The basketball __________ quit.", "answer": "coach" },
        { "prompt": "I like the __________ of the story.", "answer": "theme" },
        { "prompt": "Tulips are a __________ of flower.", "answer": "type" },
        { "prompt": "He is as strong as an __________ tree.", "answer": "oak" },
        { "prompt": "He had a sudden growth __________ .", "answer": "spurt" },
        { "prompt": "The egg __________ is very yellow.", "answer": "yolk" },
        { "prompt": "The __________ in town are nice.", "answer": "folks" },
        { "prompt": "Try to __________ for the target.", "answer": "aim" },
        { "prompt": "Coyotes hunt for __________ .", "answer": "prey" },
        { "prompt": "The __________ truck moved the car.", "answer": "tow" },
        { "prompt": "__________ wheat to make flour.", "answer": "Grind" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "3",
      "words": [
        { "prompt": "We ate __________ sandwiches.", "answer": "tuna" },
        {
          "prompt": "It's __________ duty to protect people.",
          "answer": "their"
        },
        { "prompt": "She refuses to __________ the game.", "answer": "lose" },
        { "prompt": "My dad is a man of __________ words.", "answer": "few" },
        {
          "prompt": "Laziness will __________ this project.",
          "answer": "doom"
        },
        { "prompt": "Panda bears eat __________ .", "answer": "bamboo" },
        {
          "prompt": "I need to __________ my sore muscles.",
          "answer": "soothe"
        },
        { "prompt": "The __________ were not honest.", "answer": "crooks" },
        {
          "prompt": "He didn't recognize the __________ mark.",
          "answer": "hoof"
        },
        { "prompt": "Hang your coats on the __________ .", "answer": "hooks" },
        { "prompt": "Pay at the __________ to enter.", "answer": "booth" },
        { "prompt": "The __________ explains it.", "answer": "handbook" },
        { "prompt": "Steve will __________ he is right.", "answer": "prove" },
        { "prompt": "She was __________ and said nothing.", "answer": "mute" },
        { "prompt": "Your jokes __________ me.", "answer": "amuse" },
        { "prompt": "We saw a __________ of smoke.", "answer": "plume" },
        { "prompt": "The sky was a deep blue __________ .", "answer": "hue" },
        { "prompt": "The best __________ is from the top.", "answer": "view" },
        { "prompt": "Mimi had a __________ on her leg.", "answer": "bruise" },
        { "prompt": "We formed a __________ .", "answer": "union" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "4",
      "words": [
        { "prompt": "Jerry's __________ skipped a beat.", "answer": "heart" },
        {
          "prompt": "They had to __________ to tell the truth.",
          "answer": "swear"
        },
        { "prompt": "She is __________ the spacecraft.", "answer": "aboard" },
        {
          "prompt": "I cut the brownies into __________ .",
          "answer": "squares"
        },
        { "prompt": "She __________ not to do it again.", "answer": "swore" },
        {
          "prompt": "The teacher made a seating __________ .",
          "answer": "chart"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I'm afraid they'll __________ my ideas.",
          "answer": "scorn"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "The __________ made the shirt crisp.",
          "answer": "starch"
        },
        { "prompt": "Food is a __________ of energy.", "answer": "source" },
        { "prompt": "I need money for the bus __________ .", "answer": "fare" },
        { "prompt": "She hates when I __________ in.", "answer": "barge" },
        { "prompt": "The __________ cut her finger.", "answer": "thorn" },
        { "prompt": "Jay passed the muddy __________ .", "answer": "marsh" },
        { "prompt": "The __________ of it slowed me down.", "answer": "force" },
        { "prompt": "This was a very __________ winter.", "answer": "harsh" },
        { "prompt": "Water is __________ in the desert.", "answer": "scarce" },
        {
          "prompt": "The fabric's surface was __________ .",
          "answer": "coarse"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "I see the red __________ of the rocket.",
          "answer": "flare"
        },
        { "prompt": "Track the __________ of the flight.", "answer": "course" },
        { "prompt": "The __________ had a metal blade.", "answer": "sword" }
      ]
    },
    {
      "week": "5",
      "words": [
        { "prompt": "I learned a new __________ today.", "answer": "word" },
        {
          "prompt": "It takes __________ to climb up there.",
          "answer": "nerve"
        },
        { "prompt": "__________ oil on the rusty hinge.", "answer": "squirt" },
        { "prompt": "Ken read a __________ from the poem.", "answer": "verse" },
        { "prompt": "Dana likes to surf at the beach.", "answer": "surf" },
        {
          "prompt": "The dog likes to __________ under the porch.",
          "answer": "lurk"
        },
        { "prompt": "Being a farmer is hard __________ .", "answer": "work" },
        { "prompt": "She spoke in a __________ voice.", "answer": "stern" },
        { "prompt": "The water came out in __________ .", "answer": "spurts" },
        {
          "prompt": "The car will only __________ forward.",
          "answer": "lurch"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "Try not to __________ out the answer.",
          "answer": "blurt"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "She drank to quench her __________ .",
          "answer": "thirst"
        },
        {
          "prompt": "It was a __________ of the moment decision.",
          "answer": "spur"
        },
        { "prompt": "Lecretia enjoys __________ .", "answer": "learning" },
        { "prompt": "Where did you get that __________ ?", "answer": "shirt" },
        { "prompt": "Don did well on his __________ .", "answer": "midterm" },
        { "prompt": "When will Estrella __________ ?", "answer": "return" },
        { "prompt": "The puppy tried to __________ free.", "answer": "squirm" },
        { "prompt": "The car had to __________ suddenly.", "answer": "swerve" },
        {
          "prompt": "Do you think a caged bird __________ to be free?",
          "answer": "yearns"
        }
      ]
    }
  ]
}
